[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1503_1504_Lupine",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1503_1504_d_00_container_Lupine",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1503_1504_Lupine_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1503_1504_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1503_1504_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1503_1504_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1503_1504_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1503_1504_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1503_1504_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1504_1503_Fury",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1504_1503_d_00_container_Fury",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1504_1503_Fury_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1504_1503_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1504_1503_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1504_1503_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1504_1503_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1504_1503_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1504_1503_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1502_1501_Sieged",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1502_1501_d_00_container_Sieged",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1502_1501_Sieged_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1502_1501_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1502_1501_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1502_1501_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1502_1501_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1502_1501_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1502_1501_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1502_1502_Stolen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1502_1502_d_00_container_Stolen",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1502_1502_Stolen_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1502_1502_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1502_1502_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1502_1502_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1502_1502_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1502_1502_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1502_1502_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1505_1509_Menacing",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1505_1509_d_00_container_Menacing",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1505_Artificer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1505_1509_Menacing_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1505_1509_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1505_1509_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1505_1509_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1505_1509_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1505_1509_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1505_1509_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1505_1510_Slaying",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1505_1510_d_00_container_Slaying",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1505_1510_Slaying_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1505_1510_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1505_1510_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1505_1510_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1505_1510_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1505_1510_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1505_1510_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1503_1506_Boars",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1503_1506_d_00_container_Boars",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1503_1506_Boars_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1503_1506_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1503_1506_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1503_1506_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1503_1506_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1503_1506_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1503_1506_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1510_1507_Scouting",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1510_1507_d_00_container_Scouting",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1510_1507_Scouting_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1510_1507_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1510_1507_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1510_1507_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1510_1507_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1510_1507_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1510_1507_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1510_1508_Damnation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1510_1508_d_00_container_Damnation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1504_Overseer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1510_1508_Damnation_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1510_1508_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1510_1508_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1510_1508_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1510_1508_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1510_1508_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1510_1508_f_Complete",
        "QuestArcTag": "RestlessShoreArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1510_1512_PayingRespects",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 46,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1510_1512_d_00_container_PayingRespects",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1110_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1510_1512_PayingRespects_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1510_1512_PayingRespects_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1510_1512_PayingRespects_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1510_1512_PayingRespects_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1510_1512_PayingRespects_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1510_1512_PayingRespects_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1510_1512_PayingRespects_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1502_1511_UltimateEnemy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 46,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1502_1511_d_00_container_UltimateEnemy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1502_1511_UltimateEnemy_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1502_1511_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1502_1511_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1502_1511_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1502_1511_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1502_1511_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1502_1511_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1503_1505_Hoppy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1503_1505_d_00_container_Hoppy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1503_1505_Hoppy_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1503_1505_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1503_1505_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1503_1505_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1503_1505_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1503_1505_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1503_1505_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1524_1514_FirstThing",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 42,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1524_1514_d_00_container_FirstThing",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1524_Boatswain01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1524_1514_FirstThing_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1524_1514_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1524_1514_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1524_1514_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1524_1514_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1524_1514_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1524_1514_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1524_1515_FootstepsBeach",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1524_1515_d_00_container_FootstepsBeach",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1524_Boatswain01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1524_1515_FootstepsBeach_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1524_1515_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1524_1515_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1524_1515_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1524_1515_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1524_1515_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1524_1515_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1524_1516_TrueTerror",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1524_1516_d_00_container_TrueTerror",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1524_Boatswain01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1524_1516_TrueTerror_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1524_1516_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1524_1516_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1524_1516_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1524_1516_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1524_1516_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1524_1516_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1524_1517_PiratesLife",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1524_1517_d_00_container_PiratesLife",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1510_Barkeep",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_16",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1524_1517_PiratesLife_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1524_1517_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1524_1517_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1524_1517_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1524_1517_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1524_1517_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1524_1517_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1525_1518_Communication",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 46,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1525_1518_d_00_container_Communication",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1525_AngryEarth",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1525_1518_Communication_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1525_1518_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1525_1518_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1525_1518_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1525_1518_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1525_1518_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1525_1518_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1525_1519_Ammunition",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1525_1519_d_00_container_Ammunition",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1525_AngryEarth",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1525_1519_Ammunition_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1525_1519_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1525_1519_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1525_1519_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1525_1519_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1525_1519_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1525_1519_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1525_1520_Rations",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1525_1520_d_00_container_Rations",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1525_AngryEarth",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_19",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1525_1520_Rations_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1525_1520_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1525_1520_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1525_1520_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1525_1520_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1525_1520_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1525_1520_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1526_1521_Point",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 41,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1526_1521_d_00_container_Point",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1526_Naturalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_21",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1526_1521_Point_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1526_1521_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1526_1521_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1526_1521_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1526_1521_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1526_1521_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1526_1521_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1526_1522_Breath",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1526_1522_d_00_container_Breath",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1526_Naturalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_21",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1526_1522_Breath_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1526_1522_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1526_1522_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1526_1522_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1526_1522_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1526_1522_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1526_1522_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1526_1523_ToothClaw",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1526_1523_d_00_container_ToothClaw",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1503_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_22",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1526_1523_ToothClaw_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1526_1523_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1526_1523_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1526_1523_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1526_1523_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1526_1523_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1526_1523_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1527_1524_Steadfast",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 45,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1527_1524_d_00_container_Steadfast",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1527_Wader",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_24",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1527_1524_Steadfast_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1527_1524_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1527_1524_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1527_1524_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1527_1524_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1527_1524_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1527_1524_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1527_1525_Treasured",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1527_1525_d_00_container_Treasured",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1528_Rogue",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_24",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1527_1525_Treasured_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1527_1525_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1527_1525_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1527_1525_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1527_1525_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1527_1525_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1527_1525_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1528_1526_NotAnotherFish",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 45,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1528_1526_d_00_container_NotAnotherFish",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1528_Rogue",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "15_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "15_Quest_25",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1528_1526_NotAnotherFish_Success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1528_1526_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1528_1526_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1528_1526_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1528_1526_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1528_1526_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1528_1526_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1599_1513_Nekumanesh",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 45,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1599_1513_d_00_container_Nekumanesh",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1599_Nekumanesh",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1599_1513_Nekumanesh_Success",
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1599_1513_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1599_1513_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1599_1513_b_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1599_1513_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1599_1513_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1599_1513_f_Complete"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1501_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1501_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1502_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1502_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1503_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1503_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1504_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1504_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1505_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1505_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1506_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1506_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1507_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1507_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1508_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1508_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1509_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1509_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1510_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1510_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1501_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1501_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1502_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1502_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1503_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1503_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1504_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1504_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1505_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1505_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1506_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1506_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1507_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1507_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1508_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1508_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1509_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1509_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1510_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1510_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1501_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1501_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1502_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1502_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1503_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1503_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1504_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1504_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1505_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1505_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1506_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1506_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1507_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1507_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1508_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1508_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1509_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1509_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1510_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1510_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1561_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1561_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1562_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1562_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1563_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1563_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1564_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1564_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1565_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1565_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1566_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1566_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1567_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1567_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1568_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1568_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1569_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1569_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1570_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1570_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1561_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1561_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1562_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1562_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1563_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1563_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1564_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1564_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1565_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1565_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1566_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1566_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1567_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1567_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1568_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1568_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1569_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1569_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1570_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1570_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1561_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1561_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1562_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1562_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1563_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1563_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1564_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1564_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1565_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1565_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1566_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1566_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1567_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1567_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1568_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1568_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1569_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1569_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1570_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1570_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_PoachArea_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_PoachArea_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_SpySpot_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_PoachArea_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_PoachArea_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_SpySpot_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_PoachArea_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_PoachArea_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_15_PVP_SpySpot_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_15_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_15_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_15_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 15,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_EXP_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_15_EXP_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_EXP_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_15_EXP_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_15_EXP_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_15_EXP_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]